

# FILIP TECZA



#### **ABOUT ME**

Hi, I'm Filip - I relocated to the USA 2 years ago and I'm currently a green card holder. I'm always ready for something new. Constantly improving myself by learning new languages and new skills. Looking forward to working with you!

+1 (352) 474-3600

rainbowdreamit@gmail.com

My Website

EDUCATION				
Postgraduate	Introduction to Python WSB Merito Warsaw Oct 2022 - Jul 2023 Cybersecurity WSKZ Warsaw Feb 2021 - May 2022			
Bachelor	Forensic Science and Criminology H. Chodkowska University of Technology Oct 2019 - Jul 2021			
Bachelor High School	CXIX Jacek Kuron High School 2016 - 2018			
SK	ILLS			
Selenium, Cypress		• • • • •		
HTML5, CSS3		• • • •		
SQL		• • • • •		
Python		• • • • •	•	
Data structures		• • • • •		
GIT		• • • • •		
Postman		• • • • •		
JIRA		• • • •		
Win,Mac OS		• • • • •		
CQ5 & AEM6		• • • • •		

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### University of Florida

<u>IT Analyst I</u>

10.2022-10.2023

Gainesville, Florida, USA

Testing and troubleshooting University systems. Reporting bugs and resolving automation aborts. Running SQL queries to make necessary fixes and navigate through different student databases. Writing automation scripts using UFT One in VBScript. Design specifications and coordinate integration across multiple platforms.

Worked with: Oracle SQL, UFT One, Cherwell/Jira, AQT, Slate, Appman

### **BigPicture | Appfire**

05.2021-10.2022

Warsaw, Poland

<u>Software Application Tester</u>

Testing BigPicture applications written in Angular and Java, setting up an environment for testing, writing Test Plans|Cases, writing automated test cases in Cypress, detecting and reporting bugs;

Worked with: <u>JIRA, Gerrit, Cypress, Jenkins, Postman & Kubernetes</u>

## Cheil Germany "Samsung Team"

Junior Front-End Developer

07.2020 - 10.2020

Warsaw, Poland

Implementing frontend solutions for Samsung websites (worldwide), building and developing frontend applications of managed products, constant collaboration with QA, debugging;

Worked with: <u>JS (jQuery, Slick), HTML, CSS, AEM, Adobe Xd & JIRA</u>

#### **Accenture "BMW Team"**

2017 - 2018 Warsaw, Poland

Website Content Specialist

BMW website management using CQ5, making necessary changes to HTML and JSON files following documentation from Munich headquarters, conducting

official meetings, and cooperating with Mumbai and Munich dev teams.  Worked with: HTML5, CSS3, JSON, AEM & JIRA				
ACHIEVEMENTS	LANGUAGES			
Permanent resident USA,     of the United States 2022	Polish> Native			
Google Developer     Days  Krakow, Poland 2017	English> Fluent にほんご> Learning			